{
  "currentDay": 4,
  "buckets": [
    {
      "bucketNumber": 0,
      "cards": [
        {
          "front": "kai biwi xar",
          "back": "good boy",
          "hint": "what bro is ",
          "tags": [
            "truth "
          ]
        },
        {
          "front": "test1",
          "back": "asd",
          "hint": "",
          "tags": []
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "bucketNumber": 1,
      "cards": []
    },
    {
      "bucketNumber": 2,
      "cards": [
        {
          "front": "comer",
          "back": "to eat",
          "hint": "Action",
          "tags": [
            "verb",
            "spanish"
          ]
        },
        {
          "front": "cool",
          "back": "stuff",
          "hint": "my",
          "tags": [
            "guy"
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "bucketNumber": 3,
      "cards": [
        {
          "front": "der Apfel",
          "back": "the apple",
          "hint": "Fruit",
          "tags": [
            "noun",
            "german"
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "bucketNumber": 4,
      "cards": [
        {
          "front": "merci",
          "back": "thank you",
          "hint": "Gratitude",
          "tags": [
            "phrase",
            "french"
          ]
        },
        {
          "front": "neko",
          "back": "cat",
          "hint": "Animal",
          "tags": [
            "noun",
            "japanese"
          ]
        }
      ]
    }
  ],
  "history": [
    {
      "cardFront": "der Apfel",
      "cardBack": "the apple",
      "timestamp": 1745610284578,
      "difficulty": 2,
      "previousBucket": 0,
      "newBucket": 1
    },
    {
      "cardFront": "comer",
      "cardBack": "to eat",
      "timestamp": 1745610285865,
      "difficulty": 2,
      "previousBucket": 0,
      "newBucket": 1
    },
    {
      "cardFront": "merci",
      "cardBack": "thank you",
      "timestamp": 1745610287044,
      "difficulty": 2,
      "previousBucket": 1,
      "newBucket": 2
    },
    {
      "cardFront": "neko",
      "cardBack": "cat",
      "timestamp": 1745610289169,
      "difficulty": 2,
      "previousBucket": 2,
      "newBucket": 3
    },
    {
      "cardFront": "der Apfel",
      "cardBack": "the apple",
      "timestamp": 1745610737009,
      "difficulty": 2,
      "previousBucket": 1,
      "newBucket": 2
    },
    {
      "cardFront": "comer",
      "cardBack": "to eat",
      "timestamp": 1745610738164,
      "difficulty": 2,
      "previousBucket": 1,
      "newBucket": 2
    },
    {
      "cardFront": "merci",
      "cardBack": "thank you",
      "timestamp": 1745610739237,
      "difficulty": 2,
      "previousBucket": 2,
      "newBucket": 3
    },
    {
      "cardFront": "neko",
      "cardBack": "cat",
      "timestamp": 1745610740692,
      "difficulty": 2,
      "previousBucket": 3,
      "newBucket": 4
    },
    {
      "cardFront": "cool",
      "cardBack": "stuff",
      "timestamp": 1745610743743,
      "difficulty": 1,
      "previousBucket": 1,
      "newBucket": 1
    },
    {
      "cardFront": "der Apfel",
      "cardBack": "the apple",
      "timestamp": 1745610744442,
      "difficulty": 2,
      "previousBucket": 2,
      "newBucket": 3
    },
    {
      "cardFront": "comer",
      "cardBack": "to eat",
      "timestamp": 1745610745359,
      "difficulty": 1,
      "previousBucket": 2,
      "newBucket": 2
    },
    {
      "cardFront": "merci",
      "cardBack": "thank you",
      "timestamp": 1745610746003,
      "difficulty": 2,
      "previousBucket": 3,
      "newBucket": 4
    },
    {
      "cardFront": "neko",
      "cardBack": "cat",
      "timestamp": 1745610746834,
      "difficulty": 1,
      "previousBucket": 4,
      "newBucket": 4
    },
    {
      "cardFront": "cool",
      "cardBack": "stuff",
      "timestamp": 1745610750627,
      "difficulty": 2,
      "previousBucket": 1,
      "newBucket": 2
    }
  ]
}